question_data =[
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 1988 film 'Akira', Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash's starting Pok&eacute;mon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films 'Wolf Children' and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 'Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya' series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur≈ç Araki, the same person who directed the anime Highschool of the Dead.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 'Toaru Kagaku no Railgun' anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the 'Kagerou Daze' series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The protagonist in 'Humanity Has Declined' has no discernable name and is simply referred to as 'I' for most of the series.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]